this one is my company's financial control
good weekend to you there bye
bye the guy delivers a bunch of brownie
starts to grow
this one is my box control bro
I need to fix this
is on
evolutionary
the letter is for you
I confess to you that management is not very strong in me
you don't understand the stop
call 1 friend of yours who understands
manja old
speak there
I'm you
you never one
one paid me
the other anticipated the payment and paid
the other will pay
tell you the truth
I don't even know how much I have
how much do you have to pay
that you have to pass on to my partner
I'm going crazy here
but that's it
you're a smart guy as hell
so I just want to ask you a very practical question
you already know if the operation is generating cash
if you are currently leaving no margin
you're going to be digging holes faster
my old man you can't let that happen
every Charlie Browning you sell
if he's giving money OR if he's not
because then you're going to have to adjust your business
beauty Igor
brother
I'll march here
tamo together
malandro
always follows the favela rhythm
and then how is it
I just cleaned the house
but I felt like there was one stop left
brother here o Santos
all filled
people asking for new
everything is here now
has a point of sale
this one is already running
but i need operation
big beach
Guarujá
are Vicente
lowered
in general
the Charlie Brown guys are going to storm the town
а а а
ооа оа